<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on MOJO</title><link>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on MOJO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mojo-consulting.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Web Design</title><link>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/blog/web-design/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/blog/web-design/</guid><description>Intro Values are only meaningful when applied. We&amp;rsquo;ve tried to design and build this website as a reflection of our approach to product development based on transparency, flexibility, and simplicity.
Focus Most agree that websites should be fast, responsive and usable, yet so many websites suffer from a glut of excessive software modules and dependencies.
We try to focus on the core functions of our website: providing compelling content, giving an intro to our company and services and providing a way to get in touch.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to MOJO</title><link>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/blog/welcome-to-mojo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/blog/welcome-to-mojo/</guid><description>Motivation As a team with decades of experience designing, building and deploying products we say with confidence: product development is hard. Innovation presents a daunting challenge to even the most seasoned veterans, let alone those just starting out. Successfully building a new product is a complex, messy process of harnessing a diverse set of disciplines to focus on a single objective.
Our purpose is to help everyone in the product development process excel by introducing fundamental insights, sharing powerful tools and offering top notch services for digital product development.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/about/</guid><description>Background Innovation requires a carefully balanced combination of design inspiration, business acumen and engineering skill. We exist to focus the energy of multi-disciplinary teams to help innovators make an impact and reach their audience with amazing products.
We are designers, developers and managers. We are technologists, evangelists and skeptics. We are dreamers, thinkers, and doers. The synthesis of our backgrounds is a unique understanding of the constraints and challenges of product development and a set of field-tested approaches for building solutions.</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about your goals We&amp;rsquo;d love to discuss how to design, develop and deliver your next digital product.
Book a free strategy workshop with us today to start generating solutions for your digital product goals. Please fill out the form below to get in touch.
Name E-mail address Message Send</description></item><item><title>Services</title><link>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/services/</guid><description>Discover Opportunities In a constantly evolving business environment, it is crucial to understand the market and its stakeholders. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re planning to enter a new market, launching a new service or expanding your product offering we are here to help you:
Engage potential users to understand their needs Understand the competitive landscape and analyze trends Explore emerging opportunities for innovative offerings Define Approaches Innovation lives at the intersection of creative problem solving and deep technical understanding.</description></item></channel></rss>