<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on MOJO</title><link>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on MOJO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mojo-consulting.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Web Design</title><link>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/blog/web-design/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/blog/web-design/</guid><description>Intro Values are only meaningful when applied. We&amp;rsquo;ve tried to design and build this website as a reflection of our approach to product development based on transparency, flexibility, and simplicity.
Focus Most agree that websites should be fast, responsive and usable, yet so many websites suffer from a glut of excessive software modules and dependencies.
We try to focus on the core functions of our website: providing compelling content, giving an intro to our company and services and providing a way to get in touch.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to MOJO</title><link>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/blog/welcome-to-mojo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mojo-consulting.github.io/blog/welcome-to-mojo/</guid><description>Motivation As a team with decades of experience designing, building and deploying products we say with confidence: product development is hard. Innovation presents a daunting challenge to even the most seasoned veterans, let alone those just starting out. Successfully building a new product is a complex, messy process of harnessing a diverse set of disciplines to focus on a single objective.
Our purpose is to help everyone in the product development process excel by introducing fundamental insights, sharing powerful tools and offering top notch services for digital product development.</description></item></channel></rss>